[
    {
        "question": "23 x 4",
        "answer": "92",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "17 x 6",
        "answer": "102",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 12",
        "answer": "180",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 7",
        "answer": "245",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 5",
        "answer": "120",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 3",
        "answer": "87",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 18",
        "answer": "198",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 14",
        "answer": "294",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 9",
        "answer": "171",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 8",
        "answer": "256",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 4",
        "answer": "168",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 x 6",
        "answer": "162",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 15",
        "answer": "240",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 5",
        "answer": "195",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 12",
        "answer": "300",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 3",
        "answer": "108",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 7",
        "answer": "217",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 x 13",
        "answer": "182",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 11",
        "answer": "242",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 6",
        "answer": "270",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]
